KONRAD GNAT

Software Developer | Technology Entrepreneur

KonradGnat.com | github.com/kon-rad | linkedin.com/in/konrad-gnat | KonradMGnat@gmail.com

Profile

Software developer with experience in Node.js, React, LAMP, JavaScript and Python. Highly self motivated, passionate about always learning and evolving.

Projects

All code is available to view on GitHub and links to live sites on KonradGnat.com

- Tank Battalion A 2D single and multi-player game built with vanilla ES6 JavaScript and canvas completely from scratch
- ReadBooks A instagram like app, login with social media, post and comment on books you love.
- GifNotes Winner for new business idea at GIF Hack 2017, NodeJS app that creates gifs from video using Gfycat API
- Live Sports 360 VR Winner at DeWeek Hackathon 2017 in SF, web app that live streams VR video using Wowza

Technical Strengths

Languages	Tools
Javascript, PHP, Python	NodeJS, Symfony, React, Jest, PHPUnit, Behat, MySQL, Express, Sass, Webpack, Gulp, Git,
HTML5, CSS3, Java, C	Unix, Heroku, MongoDB, JavaScript templating engines

Education

42 - Fremont, CA Apr. 2017

The "Piscine"

A 4 week programming bootcamp with a focus on C language and Unix. 42 is a rigorous, tuition free coding university located in the heart of Silicon Valley.

University of Illinois at Chicago

B.A. Major in Polish Literature and Language

Jagiellonian University - Krakow, Poland

Jun. 2010 - Aug. 2010 Jul. 2011 - Aug. 2011

Two Summer Semesters Overseas

Experience

WebToMed L.L.C. Jul. 2017 - present

Full Stack Web Developer

- Collaborating with a team of eight talented developers, crafting web applications and websites.
- Tech stack includes: PHP, Symfony, JavaScript, RequireJS, Gulp and Sass.

Freelance Web Developer Aug. 2016 - Jul. 2017

• Developed custom websites for clients using HTML5, CSS3, Javascript and PHP, typically using a Wordpress back-end.

CatechismClass.com Jan. 2017 - Jun. 2017

Web Developer Intern

- Resolved issue tickets, involving debugging and troubleshooting errors using HTML, CSS and PHP.
- Maintained and updated custom PHP framework codebase on the large production website.

Zealth Digital Marketing, Roselle, Illinois

Dec 2016 - Feb. 2017

Aug. 2009 - May 2012

Front-End Web Developer Intern

• Developed custom websites for clients using HTML5, CSS3, PHP and Javascript. Used existing PSD designs to create pixel perfect, responsive websites.

ZeroChaos, remote, short term project

Jan. 2016 - Aug. 2016

Google Search Ads Quality Rater

International Language Services Inc., Chicago

Jan. 2014 - Jan. 2016

English - Polish medical interpreter